-你错了  -你屁咧
- You're wrong. - No, I'm not.
-你就错了  -我才没有
- Yes, you are. - No, I'm not.
你来当裁判  网上会动的那些图片
Settle this. Those little animated pictures on the Internet,
是念"动图"还是"动土"
are they called "Gifs" or "Jifs"?
外国网上曾热吵过  GIF是念 "gi福" 还是"鸡福"
但无论如何  反正不是念"鸡爱a福"
图代表的是"图片"嘛
Well, the G stands for "Graphics."
很明显啊  所以我认为是"动图"
That's a hard G, so I'd say "Gif."
但发明的那男的说是念"动土"啊
W... The guy who invented it says it's "Jif."
抱歉  你是说那"男"的还是那"兰"的
I'm sorry, do you mean the guy or the juy?
我给你们三次机会
Well, I'll give you three guesses
猜我为什么很不爽
why I'm so irritated.
是不是什么事不如你愿呀
Something happened different from the way you wanted it.
看来坏事真是传千里啊
I guess news travels fast.
你猜对了  一群科学家被选去
It's true, a select group of scientists
参加一个周末学术报告会
was invited to a weekend symposium
举办地点在理查德·费曼的旧居
at a former home of Richard Feynman,
生于1918年的伟大美国物理学家
1965年的诺贝尔物理奖得主
而我居然没入选
and I wasn't included.
谢尔顿  我相信他们绝对不是因为
Oh, Sheldon, I'm sure it's not because
你并非精英科学家而没选你
they don't think you're an elite scientist.
是啊  我敢赌全部身家
Yeah, I bet you anything
绝对只是因为你是烦人精
it's just 'cause you're a pain in the ass.
你们说这些话只是为了哄我而已
You're just saying that to make me feel better.
你可以今天一整天都叽歪这事
Look, you can spend the rest of the day being bitter about this.
会的
Agreed.
我本来要接"但也可以"  但何苦浪费唇舌
I was gonna say "or," but why bother?
拉杰
Hey, Raj.
我有小礼物送你们
Hey, I got you a little gift.
这些女童军义卖饼干也太多了吧
Oh, that's a lot of Girl Scout Cookies.
你懂我  我从印度来的
You know me. I'm from India.
我抵抗不了儿童乞讨的眼神
I can't resist children begging.
房子继承权这事进展顺利吗
So, how's it going with the title to the house?
顺利  都解决了
Great, it's all done.
律师找到了我父亲
The lawyer tracked down my father
让他签字同意转让给我
and got him to sign it over.
我不需要跟他见面  也不需要跟他说话
I didn't have to meet him, I didn't have to talk to him,
我都不知道他在哪
I don't even know where he is.
所以你完全不好奇吗
Wow, so you're not curious at all?
不
Nope.
说不定他是名囚犯
What if he's in prison?
又或者是名间谍
What if he's a spy?
万一他是披头士翻唱乐队的成员呢
What if he's in a Beatles cover band?
我就说说  要是他也有你这鼻子跟发型
I'm just saying, if he's got your nose and haircut,
扮林戈一定像到爆
he'd make a killer Ringo.
再次谢谢你愿意来上节目
Thanks again for agreeing to do this.
这很酷  我从来都没上过播客
Oh, it's cool; I've never been on a podcast before.
那你的第一次选对了
Well, you picked a good one to start.
威尔有过很多很棒的来宾
Wil's had lots of great guests.
乔纳森·弗雷克斯  布兰特·史宾纳
Jonathan Frakes, Brent Spiner,
迈克·多恩  盖茨·麦克法登
Michael Dorn, Gates McFadden...
他们是《星际迷航》的人对吧
Those are Star Trek people.
没错
Yes!
我能猜出来单纯是因为完全没听过他们
I only figured that out because I've never heard of any of them.
是我自己找虐
I deserve that.
我邀请你上我节目  我还得大老远开车过来
I invited you on my show and I drove here.
抱歉
Sorry.
这个基本上就像是小型访谈节目
Okay, so, this is basically gonna be just like a little talk show.
我们会接几通听众来电
Uh, we're gonna take some calls,
我们会聊聊在拍摄
we'll talk about what it was like on the set
《杀人恶猿2》时的情况
of Serial Ape-ist 2.
应该会挺有趣的
It should be really fun.
-好兴奋啊  -是啊
- This is exciting. - Yeah.
所以大概有多少听众呢
So, how many people listen?
大多数人都是之后下载节目听
Most people download it later,
但通常实时听众大概也有个几千人吧
but usually a few thousand people listen live.
什么  有几千人
What?! A few thousand people
愿意听你说这些宅爆的东西吗
listen to you talk about nerd stuff?
又一次  话入我耳
Again, right in the ears,
直插我心
straight to the feelings.
能把盐递给我吗
Can you please pass the salt?
行
Sure.
反正我也没被邀请去理查德·费曼家
It's not like I was invited to Richard Feynman's house
也没有更重要的事情可做
and have anything better to do.
你今晚一整晚都会像这样子吗
Is this how the rest of the night's going to be?
我又不能预知未来
I don't know the future.
你觉得有可能会有
Do you think there's a chance
一颗陨石撞到地球上
that an asteroid could hit the Earth,
刚好撞烂费曼家  还撞死里面所有人吗
destroying Feynman's house and everyone in it?
不可能  谢尔顿
No, Sheldon.
那做好准备  小爷要闹脾气一整晚了
Then buckle up; you're in for a cranky night.
根据恋爱合约的附录
According to the codicil of the Relationship Agreement
你自己特别坚持要的
which you insisted upon,
我们不允许在约会之夜撅嘴闹脾气
we're not allowed to pout or be moody on date night.
你明知道我加上那条是防你大姨妈到访
You know I just put that in because of uterus stuff.
规矩对你也同样适用
Well, it applies to you, too.
我就怕你会提起这件事
I was afraid you might bring this up,
所以我钻了漏洞
so I have a work-around.
满意了吧
There you go.
就你看来  我是在笑
As far as you're concerned, I'm smiling.
虽然我不得不承认  我现在的确是在小小窃笑
Although, I must admit, I'm smiling a little bit at the moment
因为此举实在太机智了
because this loophole is so brilliant.
伯纳黛特  你想好了
So, Bernadette, have you thought
怎么重新装修这地方吗
about how you're going to redecorate this place?
我在考虑
You know, I'm thinking
拆了这地毯
ripping up the carpets,
墙纸也全部撕了
maybe lose the wallpaper,
弄新的灯架
all new light fixtures...
其实  如果你拆掉这面墙
You know, if you knocked out this wall,
你整个格局就会变成开放式的
it would give you an open floor plan,
然后...或许有点吓人  但也可能好玩
and then-- it's a little scary, but could be fun--
在这弄个室内壁炉
indoor fire pit.
我在这房子里长大
Hey, I grew up in this house, okay?
谁都不许拆任何东西
No one's knocking anything down.
行  行
Okay, okay.
等他去了漫展
When he's at Comic-Con,
我立马找个大铁球来拆
I'm bringing in a wrecking ball.
有事吗
Can I help you?
您好  请问是霍华德·沃罗威茨吗
Hi. Are you Howard Wolowitz?
是的
Yes.
这有点怪
Um, this is a little weird,
但有一个律师之前联系了我父亲
but a lawyer was trying to contact my father,
因为当时这间屋子还在他名下
because his name was still on the title for this house.
你父亲是哪位
W... uh, who's your father?
山姆·沃罗威茨
Sam Wolowitz.
山姆·沃罗威茨是我的父亲
S-Sam Wolowitz is my father.
我知道
I know.
慢着  如果我们的父亲是同一个人
Well, wait, so if we have the same father...
那你的意思是
I mean, are you saying
你是我同父异母的兄弟吗
you're my half-brother?
我想是的
I think so.
伯纳黛特  快来  这里有怪事发生
Bernadette, weird things are happening out here.
我怀疑这是一部烂片是从
I think I started to suspect it was a bad movie
我低头看剧本  看见片名的那一刻开始
when I looked at the script and saw the title,
《杀人恶猿2之猴见猴杀》
Serial Ape-ist 2: Monkey See, Monkey Kill.
剧透警告
Uh, spoiler alert:
猴子一看见啥就杀啥
after the monkey sees, it kills.
有人给我递了张小纸条
I've just been handed a note.
我把内容念一下
I'm going to read it.
"威尔  你还想来点健怡可乐吗
"Wil, do you want more Diet Coke?
对了  我们也有果汁哦"
Also, we have juice."
我不想打断你们所以递纸条
I-I didn't want to interrupt.
刚才说话的人是莱纳德
Uh, that voice you just heard belongs to Leonard,
佩妮的未婚夫
Penny's fiance.
莱纳德  你何不戴上耳机加入我们
Uh, Leonard, why don't you grab some headphones and join us?
-可以吗  -当然
- Really? - Yeah.
太棒了
Yeah, great.
趁莱纳德准备的时间
So, while Leonard gets set up,
我们接一通电话
let's take a call.
你好  这位听众  你已经连线
Hello, caller, you are on
来自《杀人恶猿2》的佩妮和威尔了
with Penny and Wil from Serial Ape-ist 2.
我没有问题要问
I don't have a question.
我只想说我非常喜欢这部电影
I just want to say I'm a big fan of the movie.
我看了大概有十次吧
I've seen it, like, ten times.
好吧  看一次  其错在我
Okay, well, I'll apologize for the first time,
但其他九次  其错在你
but the other nine are on you.
非常感谢您的来电
Thanks a lot, caller.
你知道这部电影其实有一些狂热崇拜者吗
You know that the movie actually has a little bit of a cult following.
-真的吗  -真的
- Really? - Yeah.
我在一次科幻大会上
I was at a science-fiction convention,
看见一个女人打扮成你片中半猿人的样子
and I saw a woman dressed as your half-ape character.
如果她身旁有个印度人  打扮成一根香蕉
Oh, if she was with an Indian guy dressed like a banana,
那你看见的是我的朋友  霍华德和拉杰
that was just my friends, Howard and Raj.
好了  是时候请出一位特别的嘉宾听众
All right, it's time for a very special guest caller,
我的一位友人  你们可能因为
a friend of mine, who you probably know
他是《疯狂店员》系列电影的导演而认识他
as the director of such movies as Clerks,
或在广播听过和在书上看过  他不断地提醒你
or from podcasts and books where he often reminds you that
他就是《疯狂店员》系列电影的导演
he's the guy who directed Clerks.
你好  凯文·史密斯
Hello, Kevin Smith.
伙计  一切还好吗  威尔
Hey, man, yo, is everything okay, Wil?
因为这都过了两分钟了
'Cause it's been, like, two minutes
你居然没提《伴我同行》这部电影
and you haven't even brought up Stand By Me.
该片由威尔·惠顿主演  曾荣获1987年奥斯卡奖最佳编剧提名
1987年金球奖最佳电影及最佳导演提名
凯文
Hey, Kevin!
能跟你通话让我十分激动
It's really exciting to talk to you.
真的
It really is.
你们俩真会说话  佩妮  听着
Oh, you guys are very sweet. So, Penny, listen,
我看了你的电影
I saw your movie.
可惜是部烂片
Oh, wow. I wish it was better.
别担心这点
Oh, don't worry about it.
你看过凯文的其他电影吗
Have you seen some of Kevin's films?
你这是在讨打  惠顿
You're cruisin' for a beatin', Wheaton.
总之我很爱那部人猿电影  佩妮
Anyway, man, I dug the ape movie, Penny.
我认为你在里面演得很棒
And I thought you were, like, really great in it.
我也有参演哦
You know, I'm in the movie, too.
是啊  随便啦  佩妮
Yeah, whatever. Penny!
佩妮  你怎么不多演点电影呢
Penny, how come you're not in more stuff, man?
我想都不想就会选你出演
I'd cast you in a minute.
你说真的吗
Seriously?
当然是真的
Oh, yeah, man.
其实我手上正好有部电影在前期制作中
I'm actually in pre-production on a movie right now.
跟我以前的作品相比  简直天壤之别
Way different than anything I've ever done before.
片名叫《疯狂店员3》
It's called Clerks 3.
你应该过来  试念一段台词
You should come over and read for a part.
天啊  我一定会去
Oh, my, I would love that.
你有新工作了
You have a new job.
或许我可以两边兼顾
Well, maybe I can do both.
我不认为你可以两边兼顾
I don't think you can do both.
我不认为我有问你意见
I don't think I asked you.
是啊  让他听清楚  佩妮
Yeah, you tell him, Penny.
别多管闲事  凯文·史密斯
Stay out of it, Kevin Smith.
你认为人生中是否会出现一个转折点
Do you think there comes a point in life
让你不再为被人忽略而感觉难过呢
when it stops feeling bad to be left out of things?
估计不会
Probably not.
被纳入团体活动是一种进化优势
It's an evolutionary advantage to be included in group activities.
你知道吗
You know what?
我以前挺喜欢进化的
I used to be a fan of evolution,
但在我已进化后
but I've since evolved,
现在想想其实挺蠢的
and now I think it's dumb.
被忽略会让人非常难过
Being left out is a terrible feeling.
没有人比我更了解这种感觉
No one understands that better than I do.
快听听
Hey, look at that.
即便在自己的例子里  你也是孤身一人
Even in your example, you're all by yourself.
当年在我的学校虱子肆虐的时候
When there was a lice epidemic at my school,
人人头上都有  唯独我没有
everybody got it except me.
我试着往头发上撒糖骗其他人
I tried to fool everyone by sprinkling sugar in my hair,
但下场只是被蜜蜂蛰了一顿
but I just got attacked by bees.
我可以想象他们现在在费曼旧居里的画面
I can just picture them all right now at Feynman's house,
可能  在讨论薛定谔
probably discussing Schrodinger
奥地利物理学家
于1935年提出的有关"猫既是死的又是活的"著名思想实验
同时  又不在讨论薛定谔
and at the same time, not discussing Schrodinger.
瞧
See?
他们错过了像这样有哽又有趣的笑话
They're missing out on hilarious jokes like that.
同时  又没过错
And at the same time, not.
这让我想起我的白痴哥哥姐姐
It reminds me of when my stupid brother and sister
他们在客厅搭建堡垒
would build forts in the living room
却不让我进去
and wouldn't let me in.
恨得我牙痒痒
I hated that so much.
或许
dort dort dort You know,
我不能让你获邀去参加学术报告会
there's nothing I can do about getting you invited to the symposium,
但如果你想
but if you wanted...
我们可以搭建一座堡垒
we could build a fort.
那会不会有点太幼稚了
Isn't that a little juvenile?
会比这个还幼稚吗
More juvenile than this?
我去拿毯子
I'll get the blankets.
你上网搜搜如何享受孩子般的乐趣
You Google how to have childlike fun.
我真是个不尽责的主人
You know what, I'm being a bad host.
我去加点咖啡
Let me get some more coffee.
我来吧  霍华德
Oh, let me do it, Howard.
不  我来吧
No, I got it.
乔希  你是干什么的
So, Josh, what do you do?
我在圣地亚哥学习海洋生物学
I'm studying oceanography down in San Diego.
真不错
Oh, how nice.
我可喜欢看《海底总动员》了
I loved Finding Nemo.
废话说够了
Enough chitchat.
我们怎么知道你的身份是真是假
How do we know you are who you say you are?
我为什么要撒谎呢
Why would I lie?
好吧  你问倒我了
Okay, you got me there.
你是想要钱吗
You here looking for money?
不是
No.
你想要肾  角膜  还是切一块肝
A kidney, cornea, piece of his liver?
都不是
No.
你参加了披头士翻唱乐团
You're in a Beatles cover band
你想让霍华德替代你爹扮演林戈的角色吗
and you need Howard to replace your dad as Ringo.
你还是去帮着煮咖啡吧
Why don't you help with the coffee?
好吧  可我闻到了阴谋[鱼]的味道
Okay, but something smells fishy.
不光是因为你和海洋生物一起工作哦
And not just because you work around sea animals.
那听起来挺有趣的
That actually sounds interesting,
我很乐意多听你说说
and I'd like to learn more about it.
你还好吗
Hey, you okay?
不怎么好
Not really.
这家伙突然从天而降
This guy shows up out of the blue,
于是我就有一个弟弟了
and now I have a brother?
我爸爸居然重组了一个家庭
My father has another family?
我能理解
I get it.
你现在想怎么做呢
What do you want to do?
我不知道  我
I don't know. I...
我只想让他离开
I'd just like him to go away.
我现在没法处理这件事
I can't deal with this.
好吧  包在我身上
All right, I've got your back.
谢谢你  走吧
Thank you. Come on.
告诉你
And I'd like to point out
这堵墙刚才可是保护了不少隐私呢
this wall just provided a lot of privacy!
真不敢相信我哥哥居然是个宇航员
I can't believe my brother's an astronaut.
太厉害了  感觉棒不棒
That's amazing. What was it like?
听我说  老弟
Listen, dude,
你还是走吧
it's time for you to hit the road.
喂喂  这位小兄弟刚刚提出了一个很棒的问题
Hey, hey, the young man asked a good question.
各位刚刚开始收听的听众
So, for those of you just tuning in,
我们正在直播一场生动有趣的情侣吵架
we are listening to a really fun fight
-由我的合演者  -不对不对
- between my costar... - No, no, no.
我们没有吵架  我们只是
We're not fighting; we're just...
在谈话而已
having a conversation.
好吧
All right.
我们正在直播一场生动有趣的情侣谈话
We're listening to a really fun conversation
由我在《杀人恶猿2》中的合演者
between my costar from Serial Ape-ist 2
和她不相信女性也能有梦想的未婚夫出演
and her fiance, who doesn't believe women should have dreams.
把果汁还给我
Give me back that juice.
就算我去试镜了又会怎样
What is the harm if I audition?
要是你得到那个角色了呢
Well, what if you get it?
我大概会拍部电影
I don't know, I make a movie,
变得多金又出名
become rich and famous,
将奥斯卡和金球奖纳入囊中
win an Oscar, a Golden Globe
从此过上幸福又快乐的生活吧
and live an incredibly wonderful life.
就凭一部凯文·史密斯的电影吗
From a Kevin Smith movie?
人家要挂电话了
Oh, I'm hanging up now.
别理他  老兄
Don't you listen to him, buddy.
你是最棒的
You're awesome.
你是本世纪最伟大的导演之一
You're one of the greatest directors of our time.
我没有角色给你  威顿
I don't have a part for you, Wheaton.
拜拜吧  凯文·史密斯
And that was Kevin Smith.
真是多谢你
Thanks a lot.
我只是想保护你
I'm just trying to protect you.
我见无数次你为了追求
How many times did I see you get your heart broken
女演员的梦想而伤心欲绝
trying to make it as an actress?
除了保护我  你为什么不能
Okay, instead of protecting me, why don't you try
为我的好事而开心一点呢
being excited when something good happens?
我一直都很为你高兴啊
I'm always excited for you!
你找到了这份新工作
I'm excited that you found this new job
挣到了不错的工资  我就很开心
where you're making decent money.
什么不错  我挣的钱比你多两倍呢
Decent? I make twice what you make.
什么  两倍
Wait, twice?!
是的
Yeah.
你是指  乘以2那么多吗
Like, "times two" twice?
各位听众  莱纳德刚刚发现
For those of you at home, Leonard just found out
他的未婚妻收入比他高很多
his fiance makes way more money than he does.
让我们继续听下去
Let's listen.
我读了半辈子的书
I went to school for half my life.
得到了博士学位
I have a doctorate.
现在我还在忙着还学贷
I'm still paying off college loans.
你还欠多少钱啊
Well, how much do you owe?
也许我可以帮帮你
Maybe I can help you out.
威尔  你可以把播客停一下吗
Wil, can we just turn off the podcast for a little bit?
各位听众
For those of you at home,
我现在正在摇头
I am shaking my head "no".
进行得如何啊  谢尔顿
How's it going, Sheldon?
棒极了
Wonderful!
我刚刚把灯都挂上了
I just finished hanging the lights.
我可以进来吗
Can I come in?
好呀  不过要从旁边进来
Yes, oh, but enter through the side.
蝙蝠侠毯子是用来承重的
Batman is a load-bearing blanket.
好漂亮啊
Amazing.
对吧
I know.
这可不是打印出来的哦
This isn't the printout.
这是我发自内心的笑脸
This is my real face.
我们干嘛呢
What are we doing?
这里是堡垒
This is a fort.
我们应该坐在地上
Let's sit on the floor.
来野的吗  好呀
Roughing it? Okay.
从这个角度看一切都变得好大
Everything looks so big from down here.
莱纳德平时一定就这感觉
This must be how Leonard feels.
你居然还能听见我说话
I'm surprised you could hear me
因为你的耳朵已经被薄荷糖塞住了
with this Thin Mint in your ear!
很厉害对不对
Yeah, pretty cool, huh?
对呀
Yeah.
总之  我应该告辞了
Anyway, I should probably get going.
华仔  你注意到每次你玩魔术时
Howie, have you noticed how often people say that
大家都会说同样的话吗
when you start to do magic?
抱歉  我要开很长的路回家
Sorry, I have a long drive.
希望能再次见到你
Well, I hope I get to see you again.
我也希望
I hope so, too.
我一直梦想有哥哥能陪我一起玩抛接球
I've always dreamed of having a brother to play catch with.
继续梦  别停
Keep dreaming.
我为天使队开过球
Hey, I threw out the first pitch at an Angels game.
他拿机器人干的
He did it with a robot.
你干过机器人吗
You had sex with a robot?
她不是那个意思
That's not what she meant.
但你说得也没错
But technically, yes.
等等  你赚了那么多钱
Hang on, if you're making all this money,
那钱哪去了
where is it?
在安全的地方
In a safe place.
什么意思  藏你床底下了吗
What does that mean, under your bed?
不是  是股票及债券的多元化投资组合
No, it means a diversified portfolio of stocks and bonds.
我没有太保守
I'm not overly conservative.
毕竟还年轻  理财的说我冒得了这些风险
I'm young, so my guy said I can afford to take some risks.
等等  你还有个理财的
Wait a minute, you have "a guy"?
你没有吗
Don't you have a guy?
我都没钱要什么理财的
Why would I have a guy? I don't have any money!
宝贝
Oh, sweetie,
你真应该去赚点钱了
you should really get some money.
各位听众
For those of you listening at home,
这戏老好看了
how great is this?
威尔  拜托你把那个关了吧
Wil, I'm begging you, just please turn that off.
好的
Sure.
欢迎回来
And we're back.
莱纳德  你为什么要这么在乎这些事
Leonard, why are you making such a big deal out of this?
这几年我们的角色确实有些变化
So our roles have changed a bit over the last couple years.
人生就是这样啊
This is the way life is.
风水轮流转  很快就又转回你这里了
And I'm sure in time they'll change again.
太好了  你现在不仅事业比我成功
Great, you're not only more successful than me,
人还比我成熟了
now you're more mature.
那这样  如果我做点蠢事
Okay, look, would it make you feel better
你会开心一点吗  比如我翘一天班
if I did something dumb like sneak out of work one day
去参加一下凯文·史密斯的试镜
to go audition for a Kevin Smith movie?
那就太好了  谢谢
That would be great, thank you!
我就插一下话  很快
I'm just gonna jump in here real quick.
莱纳德  就在不久前
Leonard, a moment ago,
你还极力反对佩妮重回她的演艺事业
you were dead set against Penny resuming her acting career,
现在你又全力支持了
but now you're all for it.
是不是说明她将你玩弄于股掌之中
Is it fair to say that she played you like a violin?
是的没错  威尔
Yes, it is, Wil.
我忍不住想问
So, I have to ask,
那个机器人很性感吗
was the robot sexy?
它其实就是只机械手[第4季第1集]
It was actually just a mechanical hand.
因为有只手就够了  对吧
'Cause that's all you need, right?
你真是我亲弟
You are my brother.
好  第一届年度最佳堡垒大赛
Okay, so the final four forts
最后四强为
in the first annual best fort ever contest,
或简称堡垒大对决
or "Fort off," are...
诺克斯堡
...Fort Knox,
提康德罗加堡
Fort Ticonderoga,
萨姆特堡
Fort Sumter and...
舒适毯堡
Fort Cozy McBlanket.
我认为
I'd say...
诺克斯堡力压提康德罗加堡
Knox over Ticonderoga
诺克斯堡是美国国库黄金存放处
提康德罗加堡是美国旧时极富战略意义的堡垒
因为它那有金子
'cause it's got the gold.
舒适毯堡完胜萨姆特堡
And McBlanket over Sumter
萨姆特堡曾在1861年被轰炸
随后林肯总统对南方宣战  爆发南北战争
因为它织物针数高
'cause it has a higher thread count.
十点了
10:00.
约会之夜结束了
Date night's over.
等等  不要
Wait, no.
我们还没选出冠军呢
We haven't picked a winner.
我们都知道这个堡会胜出的
We both know this one's gonna win.
确实如此
Well, of course we do.
毕竟诺克斯堡没有秘密物理学图书馆
Fort Knox doesn't have a secret physics lending library.
来  我帮你拆了
Come on, I'll help you take this down.
等等
Well, wait.
我们破例一晚
What if, just this once,
约会之夜的限制因素暂时失效
we suspend the date night parameters
你多待一会
and you stay later?
既然限制因素暂时失效
Well, as long as we're suspending the parameters,
我可以待到非常晚
I could stay really late
我们还可以第一次同居一晚
and we could have our first sleepover.
这进度相当大
That's a big step.
毕竟这么大个堡
It's a big fort.
很好
Very well.
我同意来一晚
I will agree to a family-friendly,
老少咸宜  阖家欢乐的大众级过夜
G-rated, boy-girl sleepover.
家长陪同级
Pg.
某些场景对少儿来讲过于强烈
Some scenes may be too intense for younger viewers.
老幼皆宜级
G-rated,
附有对有婴儿及幼童家庭的警示
with a warning for families with babies and toddlers.
你成功获得过夜小伙伴
You got yourself a sleepover.
用不用借你牙刷和睡衣
Do you need to borrow a toothbrush or pajamas?
我要是说为了以备不时之需
Would it alarm you to know
我两年前就在这藏好了一份过夜包
that I hid those things here two years ago
你会不会吓到
just in case this ever came up?
会的
It would,
但你知道我对充分准备是有多欣赏的
but you know how much I admire preparedness.
你怎么知道我们会在客厅睡呢
How did you know we'd be in the living room?
谁告诉你我只藏了这一份了
Who says this is the only one I hid?
有人吗  这什么东西
Hello? What is this?
我们建了个堡垒
We built a fort!
那是我床单吗
Are those my sheets?
没错
Yes, they are.
好吧
Okay.
孩子们  你们开心就好
Well, you kids have fun.
我去睡了
I'm gonna go to sleep.
莱纳德  你不想看看堡垒里面什么样子吗
Leonard, don't you want to see the inside of the fort?
不用了
Yeah, I'm good.
来嘛
Oh, come on.
我真的很想试试将人拒之门外
I really wanted to tell someone they can't come in.
好吧
Okay, fine.
谢尔顿  我能进你的堡垒参观一下吗
Sheldon, may I please visit your fort?
我想拒绝
I want to say no,
但里面太霸气了  快进来
but it's too glorious. Get in here!
谢谢
Thank you.
请在地上就座
Okay, have a seat on the floor.
那里不行  那是我的专座
Not there. That's my spot.